If some mistake has happened while taking bike, car or any other insurance in Policy Bazaar, then
how to correct it
and how much money you will have to pay to correct it, you will
see everything step by step in this video.  Whatever mistake has happened
in your insurance policy like name, address, email
ID, mobile number, payment,
you can easily correct it in this way.
So please tell us in the comments
what mistake you made.  So to
make the correction, first of all open the Policy Browser app and
simply click on the policy.
After that, whatever insurance you have taken will be
visible here.  Look,
I have insured the bike here and the
name of the bike is written as Hero Motocop DT, which
I made a mistake.  The original name of the bike
is Hero MotoCP HF DELX.  So
after clicking on this, such an interface will appear in front of you.
After that,
click on the Need Help option here.  After some time it will appear in
front of you like this and here you simply have to
click on Raise a Request.  Now
here you have to select what
correction you want to do.  I
want to change the policy details.  So I have to
click on the second option.
What mistake has happened in the policy details?  Now you have to
select here.  Take a look at
registration number, MAC, variant, email
ID, owner name, correction, mobile number,
communication, address, whatever you
want to correct, you simply have to
tap on it.  So to change the model name, we will
proceed by selecting the second option.
So after selecting the model of the bike, you have to
proceed again.
After that, two documents of the bike will have to be
uploaded here.  First of all,
take a photo of the RC of the bike and upload it and
in the second, take a photo of POIP i.e. previous year
policy i.e. the
insurance policy of the bike which was there before this and has expired and
upload it.  So
after uploading both these documents,
you have to proceed again and finally
submit the request here.  You will
get a request ID here and it will be
written below that within what date your
problem will be solved.  If you like the video, please
like and share it.